<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home</title>
    <link>https://Shbing.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 19:01:04 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://Shbing.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://Shbing.github.io/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 19:01:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Shbing.github.io/bio/</guid>
      <description>Bio Shaobing Xu is an assistant professor at the School of Vehicle and Mobility (SVM), Tsinghua University. He was an assistant research scientist (1/2019 -2/2022) and a postdoctoral researcher (10/2016-12/2018) working with Prof. Huei Peng at the Department of Mechanical Engineering (ME) and Mcity, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor. He received his Ph.D. degree in Mechanical Engineering from Tsinghua University, Beijing, China, in 2016.
His work lies at the learning, control, and design of autonomous systems with an emphasis on connected automated vehicles (CAVs).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://Shbing.github.io/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 19:01:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Shbing.github.io/publication/</guid>
      <description>Refer to Google Scholar
Selected Journal Papers  [J10] S. Xu, R. Zidek, Z. Cao, P. Lu, X. Wang, B. Li, and H. Peng, “System and Experiments of Model-Driven Motion Planning and Control for Autonomous Vehicles,” IEEE Transactions on Systems, Man, and Cybernetics: Systems, 2021. [J9] S. Xu, H. Peng, and Y. Tang, “Preview Path Tracking Control with Delay Compensation for Autonomous Vehicles,” IEEE Transactions on Intelligent Transportation Systems, 2020. [J8] S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://Shbing.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 19:01:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Shbing.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Overview of Past Work Over the past few years, Shaobing was engaged in three lines of research, i.e., scalable motion planning and control for CAVs, AI-driven sensor-level augmented reality, and eco-speed planning for automated vehicles.
  1. Motion Planning and Control of Autonomous Vehicles As a postdoc and researcher at Mcity, he developed and deployed a scalable motion planning and control algorithm/software stack for Level-4 CAVs, refer to the below figure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://Shbing.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 19:01:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Shbing.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching as Guest Lecturer  ME599-Automated and Connected Vehicle, 3 lectures on the part of vehicle dynamics and motion control, Mar 2018  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>